ecnresearch.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Policy - ECNResearch.com

By visiting this web site you are accepting the practices described in Iron Traffic, incorporated Privacy Policy. 

Iron Traffic, Inc. respects your privacy. Please be aware that we appreciate the trust you place in us by providing information on this web site, and our commitment to you is to use this information with both care and sensitivity. The information we collect from visitors to our web site helps us continually improve the products we offer to our valued customers. Types of information collected are outlined as follows:

Any information you voluntarily enter on our web site is maintained by Iron Traffic, Inc. to help us improve both the web site and product(s) advertised on the web site.

In addition, we use "cookies" (as do the vast majority of other companies that do business on the World Wide Web) when you visit our site, which are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. Information we collect and analyze via cookies includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system and platform, date and time of your visit, and cookie number. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, please review the options listed in the Help portion of the toolbar on your computer. The toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

Iron Traffic Inc. periodically sends e-mail offers to its web site visitors on behalf of other businesses. By providing information on this web site, you are agreeing to receive these periodic e-mail offers, which Iron Traffic, Inc. believes may be of interest to you as a consumer. If you do not wish to receive e-mail offers from us, please be sure to scroll down to the bottom of the first e-mail you receive and click on the opt-out link provided, which will remove your e-mail address from our database. You will then receive no further e-mail communications from us. If you do not scroll down to the bottom of the first e-mail you receive (or any e-mails thereafter), you will continue to receive e-mail offers from Iron Traffic, Inc. until you choose to click on the opt-out link that will be provided in each e-mail you receive from us.

Other than companies we have partnered with, we will not release our customers personal information. 

We will, however, release account and other personal information when such release is necessary to comply with any state, federal or international laws, or when, in our judgment, we determine it to be necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Iron Traffic, Inc. or our valued customers. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

If you have any concern about privacy at Iron Traffic, Inc.'s web site, please send us an e-mail at [info@ecnresearch.com](mailto:info@ecnresearch.com), and we will make every effort to address your inquiry in a timely manner.

Iron Traffic, Inc. reserves the right to add to, delete from or in any other way modify any or all of this Privacy Policy without prior notification.
